So when I go out and travel I can use Revolut to withdraw money for free from ATMs.
- So what are you waiting for?
Click the link in the description to download Revolut already today-
-And take part in your 250 SEK.
Thank you revolver for making assignments food possible.
Revols the financial supera app!
- There you demonstrate your skill!
What fun it has been to talk to you!
- Yes but the same you hear!
Hello then, see you on any radio channel or TV channel.
- We'll do that.
Hello!
- Welcome back!
Soon you will meet the man with this lean voice.
You will also get a Face Reveal at Alejandro Fuentes Bergström.
And meet the man who says comes to the cinema this fall.
But first, it's time for place number five.
- Now I'm sitting here with coffee, with a pier in my stomach.
Soon I will be joined by the voice that we have all heard most times in life.
Without registering it.
This voice has heard in local traffic, in telephone exchanges, on radio.
In addition, she has been crowned to be the very miss.
This iconic service that since 1934 has helped people set the clock right.
- You were a little impressive about who to meet.
13.8.8.
- That's right.
- She knows the time.
- God, you are completely embarrassed.
Hope she keeps time.
We actually said ... yes she is two minutes late.
- No, there she comes.
- There she comes!
Here she comes walking.
The trustworthy, but above all fantastic.
Johanna Herman Lundberg.
--Wow!
What a reception!
-What he also succeeded.
- Gw, the sick bastard!
- He who chats so much about that all the time.
- He got away.
- Yes, he did.
- You make the voice in the local traffic subway.
- Yeah.
I have a speaker with me.
We're going to fuck a little with people.
- Next station.
The castle.
Fun!
- Now we pull towards the subway.
Excuse me, may I ask you one thing?
After all, I still want to be a wicked Disney witch.
- But wait, this guy is pretty good at animating and drawing stuff.
After all, we could have arranged a little mini witch role for you.
We could have made a small short film where you are a wicked witch.
And I'm an innocent prince.
Or what am I?
- Innocent prince?
Yes, you can get that.
Or such a small frog or something.
- Okay, I'm a frog and you're a witch.
- Hello Hello!
I'm a nice little frog like going out.
- Now I have caught you, little ginger frog!
- What are you going to do with me?
- I need your musty frogs to complete my witch brew.
- Ouch ouch ouch!
It is hot!
It has been great fun.
-It's fine now.
- Up and down, now it is not as good anymore.
Ten years ago it was much better.
But I have a job, I should not complain.
- But you're a little out in the cold right now.
- No, not in the cold, I couldn't say that.
- You are completely alone, no one is calling.
- I am single and the children have moved.
-Are you single?
-Yes I am single.
- Ey!
- Should you and I have a quick lunch?
-I am very hungry.
- Me too!
On the way to the restaurant, we noticed that the taxi driver used a GPS with Sara's voice.
... to the ride towards the center.
- Do you usually have the GPS player's voice?
- No no votes I don't like that about 200 meters turn left no.
It's a bit goofy I think.
- Yes, it's really, really goofy.
- mhmm
- Yes, yes, yes.
- How are you?
- I feel as I deserve.
- huh?
- Yes, it was a bit AW yesterday you can say.
- So I'm scared by this shit.
I don't like this.
- Test, continue.
- What's your name?
- What do you want me to be called?
- Magdalena.
- No, for real?
No, but damn!
So, you got to get shivers.
- In a hundred meters turn right.
- Fy damn, that sounds ...
- God, you are frightened for life.
- It's cool.
- What the hell.
No, that is scary.
- Damn.
Okay, wow!
- Just make them listen.
- It feels like you are disappointed.
- But what the hell?
- She was the one who was sitting in the car.
- It's sick.
- So it's just scam?
- Yes, it's scam.
We are engaged in scams.
Maybe we should stop making people disappointed and thank you for today instead.
Maybe we should do it anyway.
- And now it's time for a historic Face Reveal on Sweden's perhaps most beloved stuffed animal.
Now it will be about the Chilean monkey Alejandro Fuentes Bergström.
He appeared on television for the first time in 2006 and has since reached a cult status in Sweden.
- Hejsan Svejsan, my name is Alejandro Fuentes-Bergström.
You are very welcome to my house.
I hope it will be good to taste.
-Otherwise?
-Yes it is good.
Yourself?
- It mopes and goes.
This is the first time I talk to a redhead guy actually
We had a scared man in the village where I grew up.
But I didn't talk to him.
I'd rather not talk about inbreeding problems.
But he could be a little violent.
- You are known for your structure.
Are you just as good at it now?
- Of course.
Thinking structure is not a fashion fly.
I think it is a matter of course to have a structure that is hardworked.
- Then Alejandro wanted to invite me to some tacos.
I note that you have patches on each bowl.
- It's better control.
If you use two different senses, then you are faster, reptile fast.
- You are so Beautiful.
I like you very much.
- Do you belong to the other kind, that you have gay?
Then I think we can continue this dinner and have a good time.
- Yes, we do so.
- Fresh cream, avocado, meat three, salad, a mock cup, small bowl and tomato square.
- Let yourself taste.
- What did you say?
- Let yourself taste?
- As I said.
- I think you have a problem that addresses that topic all the time.
You stare and try to provoke a gay from me.
- It is so difficult to determine where you are on this issue.
You are for everyone to love who they want?
- At the right time, in the right place, at the right time.
- What do you even mean at the right time?
- What time .. You have to plan a socializing.
It can't be random people you meet.
And they come to you and you have social holes about noise.
Chin Chin, Mauri.
I think you're really nice guy.
- Thanks, Alejandro.
The same, bowl.
And now my ladies and gentlemen.
Is it time for the historical moment-
-When we should meet the man behind Alejandro.
- What?
What?
What did you say?
Oh, such a thing too.
- Yes, Peace.
Or double peace.
- Oh!
- Double Peace.
You love Him, Stick to Him Like Glue.
- Scrap militarism.
War is a disaster.
It hurts me too.
And then an incredible amount of money should be spent on it.
Build roads, schools, hospitals, amusement parks.
Double Peace
- You and I Benke.
- Yes, it's you and me, Mauri.
Crikey.
- Yes, it tear well that.
- Cheers!
I actually have one thing I've dreamed about.
We on assignment food have never won a prize.
- Oh really?
- And you tend to be the one who always says who ...
- Yes, I usually talk about who has received it and who is nominated and so on.
We look for here.